Wadsworth Family Papers 1790-1950
Wadsworth Family Papers
- Persons Who Worked for the Wadsworths as Farm or Day Laborers, 1831-1842; 5 ledgers
  - Farm Accounts and Hired Hands, April, 12 1841-June 9, 1841:; D (Box unwrapped)
Wagner, Robert Ferdinand (1877-1953) Senator from New York, Telegrams (2) November 3, 1926. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Election to Senate; Congratulations on election. Box J112J F 8 Shelf 60
Wales, Mary, Emmeline's nursemaid in Boston, Letter to Mrs. Austin Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Emmeline as a child. Box LEAW2 F 26 Shelf 24
Walworth, Reuben Hyde (1788-1867) Jurist; Congressman, Letter from 12/3/1847. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Personal and Politics. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Webster, Daniel (1782-1852) Statesman and Orator, Letter from 3/29/1837. Wadsworth,Daniel (1771-1848) Personal. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Webster, Daniel (1782-1852) Statesman and Orator, Letter from 9/24/1842. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Politics. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Western, New York and Pennsylvania Railroad, Contract for gravel, June 6, 1890. Wadsworth,William Austin Railroad construction. File cabinet 1 Drawer 2
Wharton, Thomas Isaacs (1791-1856), Letters from (2) 1840-1841. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Personal. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Wheatland township, including Caledonia and LeRoy, Maps 19th century Wadsworth,James and James S Wheatland settlers and land owners. Map file, Both sets
White, David E Judge, Medina NY. Radio address text 1934. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Roosevelt, Franklin D., Opposition to. Box J112E F 27 Sb 59
White, Lawrence Grant (1887-1956) Architect, Letters from; plans(16) 1927. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Wadsworth Memorial in Temple Hill Cemetery, Geneseo. Box J112E F 34 Sh 59
Whiting, William, Agent, Letters to (50+) 1865-1869. Wadsworth family Family business. Boxes L 10-12 Shelf 16
Whiting, William, Agent, Letters to (50+) 1865-1869. Wadsworth family Family business. Boxes L 10-12 Shelf 16
Whitney, Henry, New Haven CT, Letter to September 8. 1842. Wadsworth,William Wolcott
Agent-(Book 58)
Cattle: Improving the blood line. Box LBk 1 P 138 Shelf 2
Wickes, Forsyth (1876-1964) New York Attorney, Letters (3) 1927. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Verdun Memorial for World War I; Fund raising. Box J112E F 15 Sh 59
Wild, J T Agent, Letters from (20+) 1857-1861. Wadsworth family Family business. Boxes L 8-9 Shelf 16
Willing, Thomas Mayne, Philadelphia Banker, Letters from (7) 1839-1841. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Business matters. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Willis, Nathaniel Parker (1806-1867) Author and editor, Letters from (10) 1829-1837. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Personal. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Wright, Asher (1803-1875) Indian Missionary in Buffalo, Letter from 8/8/1840. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Indian affairs. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Wright, Silas, Jr. (1795-1847) Governor of NY 1844, Letter from October 6, 1840. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Politics. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Young, Andrew White, (1802-1887) Warsaw Newspaperman, Letter from July 20, 1848. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Politics. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Young, David, Architect, Letters to (8) 1830's. Wadsworth,William Wolcott
Agent-(Book 58)
House Wm Wolcott wanted near Homestead;Cancelled contract Box L8k 1 Sh 27 indexed
Young, John (1802-1856) of Geneseo, Governor of NY 1846, Letters from (2) 3/9/1835; 5/25/1849. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Politics. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Zogbaum, Rufus Fairchild (1849-1925) Artist, naval scenes, Letters from (3) 1900. Wadsworth,William Austin Personal. Box LWAW4 F 48 Shelf 26